[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "Is it a lawsuit?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "lawsuit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "It's actually a subpoena.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "actually", "a", "subpoena", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "When was it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Just like this -- never.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "like", "this", "--", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Why are you doing this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, you invited me and I'm intrigued by you, and I'm someone who watches your show almost every night, and I'm just intrigued and also, of course, it's an opportunity to talk about empowering women, empowering minorities and the fact that we still have not won complete equality in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "invited", "me", "and", "I", "'m", "intrigued", "by", "you", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "someone", "who", "watches", "your", "show", "almost", "every", "night", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "just", "intrigued", "and", "also", ",", "of", "course", ",", "it", "'s", "an", "opportunity", "to", "talk", "about", "empowering", "women", ",", "empowering", "minorities", "and", "the", "fact", "that", "we", "still", "have", "not", "won", "complete", "equality", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria Allred", "Marco", "Goldberg"], "LOCATION": ["Allred"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Which Gloria Allred are you?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "Gloria", "Allred", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I'm the Gloria Allred who is an attorney at part of our law firm of Allred, Marco and Goldberg.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "the", "Gloria", "Allred", "who", "is", "an", "attorney", "at", "part", "of", "our", "law", "firm", "of", "Allred", ",", "Marco", "and", "Goldberg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria Allred"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "CC", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Do you believe that men and women should be absolutely equal in everything?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "men", "and", "women", "should", "be", "absolutely", "equal", "in", "everything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "I do believe that, under the law, under the Constitution of the United States, and under our public policy, that women deserve and should have a right to enjoy equal employment opportunity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "believe", "that", ",", "under", "the", "law", ",", "under", "the", "Constitution", "of", "the", "United", "States", ",", "and", "under", "our", "public", "policy", ",", "that", "women", "deserve", "and", "should", "have", "a", "right", "to", "enjoy", "equal", "employment", "opportunity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Do you ever do anything for publicity?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "do", "anything", "for", "publicity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "We do cases of public interest and importance.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "cases", "of", "public", "interest", "and", "importance", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Or should there be equality because simply because a woman may not have the power of a man to play to that ability?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "should", "there", "be", "equality", "because", "simply", "because", "a", "woman", "may", "not", "have", "the", "power", "of", "a", "man", "to", "play", "to", "that", "ability", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "It really depends on the particular facts.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "really", "depends", "on", "the", "particular", "facts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you feel as aggrieved for men who get treated badly by women bosses?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "as", "aggrieved", "for", "men", "who", "get", "treated", "badly", "by", "women", "bosses", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "Well, we have --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Or is it all women against men?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "all", "women", "against", "men", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, we actually have had a number of cases, where we represent men who have been discriminated against in employment, on account of their gender.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "actually", "have", "had", "a", "number", "of", "cases", ",", "where", "we", "represent", "men", "who", "have", "been", "discriminated", "against", "in", "employment", ",", "on", "account", "of", "their", "gender", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Does that worry you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "worry", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "No, not at all, because we are a plaintiff's law firm.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", ",", "because", "we", "are", "a", "plaintiff", "'s", "law", "firm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you like that status?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "that", "status", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well, I like empowering my clients.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "like", "empowering", "my", "clients", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Why did you feel compelled to expose him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "feel", "compelled", "to", "expose", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, it matters if any man hurts any woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "matters", "if", "any", "man", "hurts", "any", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "She was a porn, right?", "question_tokens": ["She", "was", "a", "porn", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "They had -- she had -- she was an adult film star, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "had", "--", "she", "had", "--", "she", "was", "an", "adult", "film", "star", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And I just wonder sometimes, when you watch what she did afterwards, do you slightly sit back and go, maybe I should have left that one alone?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "just", "wonder", "sometimes", ",", "when", "you", "watch", "what", "she", "did", "afterwards", ",", "do", "you", "slightly", "sit", "back", "and", "go", ",", "maybe", "I", "should", "have", "left", "that", "one", "alone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Do you ever regret afterwards taking on cases, because of the way that perhaps the person you've been defending or prosecuting on behalf of, because of their behavior afterwards, you have moments of self-reflection afterwards?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "regret", "afterwards", "taking", "on", "cases", ",", "because", "of", "the", "way", "that", "perhaps", "the", "person", "you", "'ve", "been", "defending", "or", "prosecuting", "on", "behalf", "of", ",", "because", "of", "their", "behavior", "afterwards", ",", "you", "have", "moments", "of", "self-reflection", "afterwards", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "No, I'm so proud of my clients and the courage they've shown.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "so", "proud", "of", "my", "clients", "and", "the", "courage", "they", "'ve", "shown", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Does she -- does she not care about Ms. Woods?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "--", "does", "she", "not", "care", "about", "Ms.", "Woods", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Of course, she did.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ms. Woods"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "But do you care about women being hurt by men whom they trusted, whom they loved, who they had every reason to believe loved them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "care", "about", "women", "being", "hurt", "by", "men", "whom", "they", "trusted", ",", "whom", "they", "loved", ",", "who", "they", "had", "every", "reason", "to", "believe", "loved", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "I get that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Ever?", "question_tokens": ["Ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "They have to survive.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "to", "survive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Or is it always strictly legal?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "it", "always", "strictly", "legal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, we represent victims' rights.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "represent", "victims", "'", "rights", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 274, "question": "Should having an affair preclude a man from running for office?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "having", "an", "affair", "preclude", "a", "man", "from", "running", "for", "office", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "I think that if --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "if", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "EX", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "So, where do you draw the line?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "where", "do", "you", "draw", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, I think that politicians, if they are going to seek the highest office in our land, the presidency of the United States of America, they need to be honest with the American public, and just put it all out there, and not be hypocrites, not present themselves as the perfect family man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "politicians", ",", "if", "they", "are", "going", "to", "seek", "the", "highest", "office", "in", "our", "land", ",", "the", "presidency", "of", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", ",", "they", "need", "to", "be", "honest", "with", "the", "American", "public", ",", "and", "just", "put", "it", "all", "out", "there", ",", "and", "not", "be", "hypocrites", ",", "not", "present", "themselves", "as", "the", "perfect", "family", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Are you happy for him to restart politically, if you like?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "happy", "for", "him", "to", "restart", "politically", ",", "if", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, let me just say -- I mean, I'm not a person who's going to vote for any of the potential Republican nominees for the presidency of the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "just", "say", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "person", "who", "'s", "going", "to", "vote", "for", "any", "of", "the", "potential", "Republican", "nominees", "for", "the", "presidency", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What happened to that guy that raped you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "to", "that", "guy", "that", "raped", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Did you ever see or hear of him again?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "see", "or", "hear", "of", "him", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I never did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "You never found out what happened to him?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "found", "out", "what", "happened", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Never found out.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "found", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What are your feelings towards him now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "feelings", "towards", "him", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "LLRED: You know, I generally don't look back.", "answer_tokens": ["LLRED", ":", "You", "know", ",", "I", "generally", "do", "n't", "look", "back", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Were you able to forgive your first husband for the abuse when you discovered about this bipolar?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "able", "to", "forgive", "your", "first", "husband", "for", "the", "abuse", "when", "you", "discovered", "about", "this", "bipolar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "You know, it wasn't about forgiving.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "about", "forgiving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "How great is my mom?", "question_tokens": ["How", "great", "is", "my", "mom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "She's pretty special, your mother.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "pretty", "special", ",", "your", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "She's given it to you, hasn't she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "'s", "given", "it", "to", "you", ",", "has", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Does she?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I'll answer, too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "answer", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "And no one can remember when I took a vacation --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "no", "one", "can", "remember", "when", "I", "took", "a", "vacation", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 427, "question": "You never have a vacation?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "have", "a", "vacation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I've had a vacation -- well, years ago, I took my grandchildren on vacations --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "had", "a", "vacation", "--", "well", ",", "years", "ago", ",", "I", "took", "my", "grandchildren", "on", "vacations", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "ORGAN: Why?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Because I have too much to do to fight injustice that still exists for my clients, for women and minorities.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "too", "much", "to", "do", "to", "fight", "injustice", "that", "still", "exists", "for", "my", "clients", ",", "for", "women", "and", "minorities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "You have a 10-year-old car, is that true?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "10-year-old", "car", ",", "is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 463, "question": "But then -- but then I come back to the Tiger Woods case that you heard us debating earlier where I kind of think, why would this women, who does all this incredible stuff, take on a porn star to basically flim/flam Tiger Woods, really?", "question_tokens": ["But", "then", "--", "but", "then", "I", "come", "back", "to", "the", "Tiger", "Woods", "case", "that", "you", "heard", "us", "debating", "earlier", "where", "I", "kind", "of", "think", ",", "why", "would", "this", "women", ",", "who", "does", "all", "this", "incredible", "stuff", ",", "take", "on", "a", "porn", "star", "to", "basically", "flim/flam", "Tiger", "Woods", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJR", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Can I -- let me respond to that, Piers, because --", "answer_tokens": ["Can", "I", "--", "let", "me", "respond", "to", "that", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger Woods", "Tiger Woods"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I'll tell you what I think.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Or the age discrimination case that we won?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "the", "age", "discrimination", "case", "that", "we", "won", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Most of what she does.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "of", "what", "she", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Were you as proud?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "as", "proud", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "May I finish, please?", "question_tokens": ["May", "I", "finish", ",", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Then why are you saying \"porn star,\" as if that's relevant?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "why", "are", "you", "saying", "``", "porn", "star", ",", "''", "as", "if", "that", "'s", "relevant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "``", "NN", "NN", ",", "''", "IN", "IN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I'm just wondering whether, when your mother takes on a case like that, which is obviously so high-profile, obviously going to get so much attention, when you see this victim as she's being portrayed, go on to make another movie --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "wondering", "whether", ",", "when", "your", "mother", "takes", "on", "a", "case", "like", "that", ",", "which", "is", "obviously", "so", "high-profile", ",", "obviously", "going", "to", "get", "so", "much", "attention", ",", "when", "you", "see", "this", "victim", "as", "she", "'s", "being", "portrayed", ",", "go", "on", "to", "make", "another", "movie", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger Woods"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Well, so what?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "so", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "-- in which she uses Tiger Woods --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "in", "which", "she", "uses", "Tiger", "Woods", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "And exploit it and commercialize it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "exploit", "it", "and", "commercialize", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "And she's a victim.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "she", "'s", "a", "victim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "And why don't you spend as much talking about the fact that Tiger Woods should apologize to the women that he hurt?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "do", "n't", "you", "spend", "as", "much", "talking", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "Tiger", "Woods", "should", "apologize", "to", "the", "women", "that", "he", "hurt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "He did apologize.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "apologize", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger Woods"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Well, do you like having this famous, infamous mother?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "do", "you", "like", "having", "this", "famous", ",", "infamous", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I love my mother.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "my", "mother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Does she get mischaracterized, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "get", "mischaracterized", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "How much of that is her own fault for taking on cases which are inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "that", "is", "her", "own", "fault", "for", "taking", "on", "cases", "which", "are", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "None.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Why does your mother take on celebrity cases?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "your", "mother", "take", "on", "celebrity", "cases", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "RP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Listen, we're talking about the media.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "we", "'re", "talking", "about", "the", "media", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Can you not persuade your mother to drop all the scandalous celebrity cases?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "not", "persuade", "your", "mother", "to", "drop", "all", "the", "scandalous", "celebrity", "cases", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Because I don't consider them to be scandalous celebrity cases.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "do", "n't", "consider", "them", "to", "be", "scandalous", "celebrity", "cases", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "They're not scandalous celebrity cases.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "not", "scandalous", "celebrity", "cases", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "LOOM: The media -- because I care about them and they have viable -- they're human beings, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["LOOM", ":", "The", "media", "--", "because", "I", "care", "about", "them", "and", "they", "have", "viable", "--", "they", "'re", "human", "beings", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love, Gloria?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", ",", "Gloria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "ORGAN: Is it a lawsuit?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "it", "a", "lawsuit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "It's actually a subpoena.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "actually", "a", "subpoena", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Would you like to fall in love again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "fall", "in", "love", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "No, I don't have time, and I don't want to make that investment.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "have", "time", ",", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "make", "that", "investment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Much younger men.", "answer_tokens": ["Much", "younger", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120323pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", ",", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "We have a saying in the women's movement, become the person you wanted to marry.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "a", "saying", "in", "the", "women", "'s", "movement", ",", "become", "the", "person", "you", "wanted", "to", "marry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]